Matheus Hugolini Carneiro

Application Developer

Contact

Github: <u>mathugolini</u> LinkedIn: <u>matheus-hugolini</u>

Telephone: 11 93458-7332 Email: mathugolini@gmail.com

Education

Bachelor Degree – Information Systems FIAP, BR – São Paulo 2020 - 2023

Diploma – Customer Service Greystone College, CA – Toronto 2018-2019

Salesforce Administrator Certification Salesforce Associate Certification Azure AZ-900 Certification

Profile

Experience as a Developer and Quality Assurance participated in projects for companies in the telecommunications and oil fields. Improving my skills to meet customer needs and assist the team using agile methodologies. With solid international experience and fluent English. Expertise in Salesforce, Java, and Cloud

Skills

• Java | Docker | Cloud | JavaScript | SQL | SpringBoot | Apex | LWC

Work Experience

IBM Brazil, São Paulo Application Developer

October 2022 - June 2023

Enterprise Management Project at Petrobras, responsible for implementing solutions using Salesforce and integration with Java legacy systems, with focus and digital signature.

Technologies: Java, Web Applications, SQL, Apex, LWC, Data Structures.

Consultant Salesforce

April 2022 - September 2022

Solar project at Claro, a representative in the Quality Assurance area, also working in Salesforce development, configuration, and automation of processes in the Journey and Customer Catalog.

Technologies: Test Automation, Validation Rules Flow and Flow Rules, CI/CD, HTML, CSS, JS.

Internship IBM

February 2022 - April 2022

Responsible for conducting agile ceremonies, troubleshooting, setting goals and prioritizing tasks, surveying documentation, reporting results, and applying good communication.

Technologies: Git, Salesforce, Java Jira, Trello, Slack, Microsoft Teams.

Sprint Canada, Toronto (Canada) Customer Service Representative

June 2019 - December 2019

Experience with customer service, communication in English, maintained customer retention, working on problem-solving, sales, and encouragement.